Jones, Howard Palfrey; Papers apap070
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Howard Palfrey Jones Papers
1917-1973
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Jones, Howard Palfrey, 1899-1973
apap070
27 cubic ft.
This collection documents many aspects of the career of Howard Palfrey Jones, including work in the civil service in New York State, foreign service, and with local governments.
Biographical History
Howard Palfrey Jones (1899-1973) had an active political career, serving as an officer in the National Municipal League, director of the New York State Commission on Revision of Tax Laws, and head of the New York State Civil Service Commission. He was an officer in the U.S. Foreign Service where he served as ambassador to Indonesia. He was also an editor, professor of journalism at the University of Michigan and New York University, and author of the book Indonesia: The Possible Dream.
Scope and Contents
The collection includes press releases, texts of Herbert Hoover's speeches, and reports from the U.S. Food Administration, 1917-1918; correspondence, articles, and speeches, 1930-1942; reports from legislative committees on municipal finances, law reform, and management, 1940-1973. The collection also documents Howard Palfrey Jones's career as an officer of the National Municipal League, 1929-1939; director of the New York State Commission on Revision of Tax Laws, 1936-1938; head of the New York State Civil Service Commission, 1939-1943; and as a U.S. Foreign Service officer in Germany, China, and Indonesia, 1948-1965.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is not processed. It has no series and is arranged alphabetically at the box level.
Acquisition Information
1970 Most items in this manuscript group were donated to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives, by Howard Palfrey Jones.
1976 Additional materrial was added by George R. Colley.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted.
Public Servants; Diplomatic and consular service, American; Taxation -- Law and legislation -- New York (State); Civil service -- New York (State); Correspondence; Speeches; Articles; Jones, Howard Palfrey, 1899-1973; National Municipal League; New York (State). Commission on Revision of Tax Laws; New York (State). Civil Service Commission; United States. Foreign Service; United States Food Administration
- Abstracts From University of Rochester, Education, Undated (Box 1 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Albany Area Budgets, Undated (Box 1 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- American, Undated (Box 1 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 3)
- American Labor Party, Bulletins, etc., Undated (Box 1 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 4)
- Anecdotes, Undated (Box 1 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 5)
- The Annals, Undated (Box 1 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 6)
- Annual Executive Conference of Joint Committee on Interstate Cooperation, Undated (Box 1 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 7)
- Application for Employment and Other Forms - California, Undated (Box 1 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 8)
- Arrow Street Guide - Buffalo, Undated (Box 1 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 9)
- Banking Department, Undated (Box 2 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Barter, Undated (Box 2 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- Bills Paid, Undated (Box 2 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 3)
- Book List, Undated (Box 2 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 4)
- Doug Brinkley's Impression of Germany, Undated (Box 2 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 5)
- Buffalo Area - Bonded Debt Information, Undated (Box 2 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 6)
- Buffalo Area- Cities - Financial Statements and Budgets - Alto Villages, Undated (Box 2 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 7)
- Buffalo Area - Town Governments, Undated (Box 2 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 8)
- Buffalo Niagara Area General, Undated (Box 2 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 9)
- Bulletins - Hamburg World Economic Archives, Undated (Box 3 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Cattatagus County - New York: A Plan for Personnel Administration, Undated (Box 4 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Central Press, Undated (Box 4 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- Central Press Association, Undated (Box 4 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 3)
- Central Press (Old), Undated (Box 4 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 4)
- Central Press Old Sources of Material, Undated (Box 4 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 5)
- Charts, Diagrams, Documents, Undated (Box 5 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Charts, Diagrams, Documents, Undated (Box 6 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Christmas Cards, Undated (Box 7 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- City and the Citizen, Undated (Box 8 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- City Club of New York, Undated (Box 8 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- City Manager Book, Undated (Box 8 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 3)
- Civil Service Laws of Ohio, Undated (Box 8 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 4)
- The Civil Service Law - New York State, Undated (Box 8 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 5)
- Columbia University, Undated (Box 9 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Columbia University Club, Undated (Box 9 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- Columbia University Information, Undated (Box 10 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Conversation -The Child and Family in Court, 1939 (Box 10 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- Cooperatives/Receipts, Undated (Box 10 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 3)
- Correspondence & General, Undated (Box 10 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 4)
- Cosmos Club, Undated (Box 10 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 5)
- County Children's Court Act, Undated (Box 10 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 6)
- Debt Statistics, Undated (Box 11 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Democratic Party, Undated (Box 11 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- Desmond, Robert W, Undated (Box 11 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 3)
- Detroit East Side Association Papers, Undated (Box 11 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 4)
- Drizari, Nelo, Undated (Box 11 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 5)
- Editing and Publishing The Community Paper, Undated (Box 12 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Editor and Publisher The Fourth Estate, Undated (Box 12 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- 1924 Election Papers - Evansville Press, Financial Control, Forbes (Box 12 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 3)
- Freedom of the Press, Undated (Box 12 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 4)
- Germany, Undated (Box 13 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Germany's Economic Situation, 1935 (Box 13 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- Governmental Control - Tenth Report, Undated (Box 13 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 3)
- Highway Map (Brie County), Undated (Box 14 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- History of Reforms, Undated (Box 14 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- Homes, Undated (Box 14 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 3)
- Income Tax - Federal and State, Undated (Box 14 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 4)
- Index Cards, Undated (Box 15 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Insurance Automotive, Undated (Box 16 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Insurance Fire, etc., L, Undated (Box 16 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- International Conference at Lyons - Booklet and Report, Undated (Box 16 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 3)
- Interstate Cooperation - New York State Committee On, Undated (Box 17 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Jones, H. P., Articles and Speeches, Undated (Box 18 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Jones, H. P., Articles Before 1932, Undated (Box 18 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- Jones, H. P. Articles, 1932-1933 (Box 19 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Jones, H. P. Articles and Speeches, 1934 (Box 19 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- Jones, H. P. Articles and Speeches, 1935-1936 (Box 19 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 3)
- Jones, H. P. Articles and Speeches, 1937-1938 (Box 20 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Jones, H. P. Articles and Speeches, 1939 (Box 20 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- Jones, H. P. Books, Undated (Box 20 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 3)
- Jones, H. P. Congratulations, Undated (Box 20 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 4)
- Jones, H. P. Constitutional Convention Campaign, Undated (Box 21 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Jones, H. P. Expense Accounts, Undated (Box 21 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- Jones, H. P. Fiction, Undated (Box 21 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 3)
- Jones, H. P. Miscellaneous Items, Undated (Box 22 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Jones, H. P. Miscellaneous Items, Undated (Box 23 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Jones, H. P. Outlines and Ideas for Speeches and Articles, Undated (Box 24 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Jones, H. P. Political Speeches, Undated (Box 24 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- Jones, H. P. Speeches - Correspondence, Undated (Box 24 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 3)
- Jones, H. P. Thesis, Undated (Box 24 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 4)
- Journalism Schools, Courses, Undated (Box 24 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 5)
- Kansas Government Journal, Undated (Box 17 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- Labor Club, Undated (Box 17 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 3)
- Legal Schedules, Undated (Box 17 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 4)
- Licenses, Papers, etc., Undated (Box 17 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 5)
- Local Government - Europe, Undated (Box 17 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 6)
- Lotus Club, Undated (Box 17 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 7)
- Masons - Montauk Lodge, Undated (Box 25 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Mastick Commission Expenses, Undated (Box 25 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- Mastick Commission Minutes, Undated (Box 25 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 3)
- Mastick Commission, 1938 (Box 25 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 4)
- Mauck, Undated (Box 25 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 5)
- Men's Faculty Club - Columbia, Undated (Box 26 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Merit System Council of Colorado, Undated (Box 26 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- Michigan, University of, Undated (Box 26 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 3)
- Mission Corporation, Undated (Box 26 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 4)
- Money, Undated (Box 26 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 5)
- Mooney, Undated (Box 26 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 6)
- Moore, Frank C, Undated (Box 26 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 7)
- Municipal Credit Papers, Undated (Box 26 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 8)
- Municipal Report, Undated (Box 26 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 9)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, AM-AZ, Undated (Box 27 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, BL-BZ, Undated (Box 27 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, CA-CHR, Undated (Box 28 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, CHU-CL, Undated (Box 28 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, COA-CZ, Undated (Box 28 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, D-DH, Undated (Box 28 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, DI-DZ, Undated (Box 28 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, FR-FZ, Undated (Box 29 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, H, Undated (Box 29 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, HE-HZ, Undated (Box 29 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, I, Undated (Box 29 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, K, Undated (Box 30 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, L, Undated (Box 30 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, M, Undated (Box 30 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, MC, Undated (Box 30 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, MI-MZ, Undated (Box 31 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, N, Undated (Box 31 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, O, Undated (Box 31 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, P, Undated (Box 31 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, PO-PZ, Undated (Box 31 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, R, Undated (Box 31 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, RI-RZ, Undated (Box 32 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, S, Undated (Box 32 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, SI-SP, Undated (Box 32 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, T, Undated (Box 32 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, U, Undated (Box 33 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, V, Undated (Box 33 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, W, Undated (Box 33 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, WE-WH, Undated (Box 33 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, WI-WR, Undated (Box 33 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous German Literature, Undated (Box 34 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous German Literature, Undated (Box 35 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous German Literature, Undated (Box 36 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous German Literature, Undated (Box 37 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous Papers - "Contempt of Court and Freedom of the Press:" by HPJ, Undated (Box 38 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous Papers, Letters, 1925-1928 (Box 39 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- NAACP, Undated (Box 40 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Nanson's Proportional Representation - Excerpt from the Nation, Undated (Box 40 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- Nanson Systems - Preferential & Hare List, Undated (Box 40 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 3)
- The Nation, Undated (Box 40 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 4)
- National Association of Civic Secretaries, Undated (Box 40 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 5)
- National Civic Federation, Undated (Box 40 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 6)
- National Committee on Municipal Standards, Undated (Box 40 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 7)
- National Conference of Social Work, Undated (Box 40 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 8)
- National Conference on Government, 1931 (Box 40 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 9)
- National Conference on Science of Politics, Undated (Box 40 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers))
- National Consumers Cooperative Association, Undated (Box 40 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers))
- National Economic League, Undated (Box 41 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- National Education Association, Undated (Box 41 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- National Federation of Uncle Sam's Voters, Undated (Box 41 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 3)
- National Highways Association, Undated (Box 41 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 4)
- Howard Palfrey Jones Papers, Undated (Box 41 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 5)
- National Labor Party, Undated (Box 41 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 6)
- National League of Women Voters, Undated (Box 41 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 7)
- National Municipal League - Committee on State Government, Undated (Box 42 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- National Municipal League - Harris Monograph, Undated (Box 42 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- National Municipal League - Model Charter Revision, Undated (Box 42 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 3)
- National Municipal League - New York State Committee, Undated (Box 42 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 4)
- National Municipal League - Organization Membership, Undated (Box 43 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- National Municipal League - P R Committee, Undated (Box 43 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- National Municipal League - P R Department Membership, Undated (Box 43 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 3)
- National Municipal League, 1930-1939 (Box 43 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 4)
- National Municipal League, 1940-1946 (Box 43 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 5)
- National Popular Government League, Undated (Box 44 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- National Printer Journal, Undated (Box 44 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- National Self Government Committee, Undated (Box 44 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 3)
- National Single Tax League, Undated (Box 44 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 4)
- National Social Unit Organization, Undated (Box 44 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 5)
- National Student Forum, Undated (Box 44 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 6)
- National Voter's League, Undated (Box 44 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 7)
- National Woman's Party, Undated (Box 44 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 8)
- National Women's Trade Union League, Undated (Box 44 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 9)
- Nazi Literature, Undated (Box 45 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- New Jersey Municipalities, Undated (Box 45 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- New Jersey State Federation Of Labor, Undated (Box 45 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 3)
- New Jersey Teachers Association and Union, Undated (Box 45 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 4)
- New Outlook, Undated (Box 45 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 5)
- New Republic, Undated (Box 45 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 6)
- New Student, Undated (Box 46 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- New York City Area - General, Undated (Box 46 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- New York City Citizens Union, Undated (Box 46 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 3)
- New York City Club, Undated (Box 46 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 4)
- New York City Young People's Socialist Club, Undated (Box 46 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 5)
- New York City League of Women Voters, Undated (Box 46 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 6)
- New York Civic Club, Undated (Box 46 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 7)
- New York Industries, Undated (Box 46 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 8)
- New York Life, Undated (Box 46 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 9)
- New York State Farm Labor Party, Undated (Box 46 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 10)
- New York State Newspapermen Conference, Undated (Box 46 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 11)
- Newmont Mining Corporation, Undated (Box 46 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 12)
- News in Brief (Reports and Documents of Contemporary Germany), Undated (Box 47 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Nonpartisan Elections, Undated (Box 47 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- Nonpartisan League, Undated (Box 47 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 3)
- Numbering Machines, Undated (Box 47 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 4)
- Nyack National Bank and Trust Company, Undated (Box 47 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 5)
- Oddities, Undated (Box 47 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 6)
- Periodicals - Friends of Europe, Undated (Box 48 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Periodicals - New York State, Undated (Box 48 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- Personal. Addressed to Jones at National Municipal Review Board from H Gund., Undated (Box 49 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Carl H. Pforzheimer and Company, Undated (Box 49 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- Picture and Etchings, Undated (Box 49 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 3)
- Population Tables, Undated (Box 49 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 4)
- Press, Undated (Box 49 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 5)
- Personal Correspondence, 1927-1928 (Box 50 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Personal Correspondence, 1960s-1970s (Box 50 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- Rendall, Undated (Box 51 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- 27th Report of Ohio Civil Service Commission, Undated (Box 51 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- Reports To Commission and Minutes, Undated (Box 51 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 3)
- The Republican Party, Undated (Box 51 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 4)
- Riverside Neighborhood News - Patsy's, Undated (Box 51 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 5)
- Rochester Area, Undated (Box 51 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 6)
- Rockland County, Undated (Box 52 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Rockland County News Clippings, Undated (Box 52 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- Russian Paper, Undated (Box 52 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 3)
- School of District Data, Undated (Box 52 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 4)
- Sigma Delta Chi, Undated (Box 52 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 5)
- Sigma Nu, Undated (Box 52 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 6)
- Smashing the Rackets - Dewey's Story, Undated (Box 52 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 7)
- Speech By Hitler, 1935 (Box 52 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 8)
- State Agencies & Lawmaking, Undated (Box 52 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 9)
- State Government Magazine, Undated (Box 52 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 10)
- Stone and Webster, Undated (Box 52 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 11)
- Street Bus Guide/Map (White Plains), Undated (Box 52 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 12)
- Supplement to Public Assistance Manual of Erie County, Undated (Box 53 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Syracuse Area, Undated (Box 53 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- Tax Limitation, Undated (Box 53 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 3)
- Tax Policy League, Undated (Box 53 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 4)
- Technocracy, Undated (Box 53 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 5)
- Temporary Salary Board - Fifth Report for New York State, Undated (Box 53 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 6)
- Uniform City Court Act, Undated (Box 53 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 7)
- United Corporation, Undated (Box 53 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 8)
- United States Food Released' Data, Undated (Box 54 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- United States Treasury Department, Undated (Box 54 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- University Club, Undated (Box 54 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 3)
- Utica Area, Undated (Box 54 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 4)
- Vouchers - Expense, Undated (Box 55 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- W R K & Taylor Company, Undated (Box 55 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- Weekly Report of German Institute For Business Research, Undated (Box 56 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- What Policy Education?, Undated (Box 57 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 1)
- Wisconsin, University of, Undated (Box 57 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 2)
- Wisconsin Savings, Loan and Buildings Association, Undated (Box 57 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 3)